<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Material3</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="homeText">
        Material Design is Google\'s design language, created in 2014.
    </string>

    <string name="articleText">
        Material Design is Google\'s design language, created in 2014.
        It\'s a set of guidelines put together by Google to improve the overall
        look and feel of Android apps with consistent design practices.
        Material You, its latest version, is marking a brand new approach to app design.
        One that can be dynamically personalized to each users tastes.\n\n
        With Material You, Google ambition is to help all designers
        create designs that are personal for every style
        accessible for every need, alive and adaptive for every
        screen And bring back creativity and excitement for Android apps.
        In a Fast Company interview, Google VP of design Matias Duarte declared
        The material metaphor was maybe too good
        and the paper has come to dominate our interfaces.\n\n
        They are consistent…but they\'ve gotten a little stale
        boring, too tied to a modernist same-ism that is spread everywhere."
        From now on, apps and widgets can be customized based on users
        wallpaper colour palettes.
        Whats particularly smart about this approach is that it doesn't
        require additional efforts from the users
        given that most of us already customize our wallpaper.\n\n
        Material You also makes it easier for designers
        to build responsive and accessible apps
        offering users more control over the contrast size
        and spacing settings. Let's take a closer look..\n\n
        Dynamic Colours
        Material Design 3 is undeniably a bold update
        and its most exciting change is dynamic colours. Here's how it works.
        Material Design 3 has a built-in colour combination feature
        that extracts colours from users' wallpaper images. \n\n
    </string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="article">Article</string>
</resources>